Scientists are unaware why,
but twelve thousand years ago humanity got tired of walking around,
decided they were going through a lot right now,
and needed some personal space,
thus inventing houses!
They founded civilization and immediately thought (with all certainty) that they were
on this (with all certainty) flat earth.
But then several thousand years later,
everyone changed their minds about the first two categories on the exact same day.
Coincidentally, it was the exact same day
reality TV was first broadcasted!
But the truth is humans aren't most evil animal either.
I can explain, but first let's talk about the other two.
Chapter One: The best animal is obviously
THE ALPACA.
I would present my argument for this,
but I highly doubt anyone's arguing against me.
Chapter Two: The smartest animal is
THE RED PANDA.
This I can argue for.
Did you know that red pandas are expert at camouflage,
even though they have bright red fur?
Did you know red pandas are masterful problem solvers?
Did you know they once controlled
the greatest space empire this galaxy has ever seen,
and caused the rise of human civilization?
Yes, these are all true.
I have never stated that I am an unreliable narrator.
The empire is now gone. Let me tell you how.
Red pandas come from the star system "Star System."
Unlike humans, the first time they saw the yellow ball, they called it!
They named themselves "Red Pandas," in case some other animal in the universe had already used the name "Panda."
Their home world was called "Mountains,"
called that because our planet is called "Earth."
It's not rocket science
(which is something the cat-bears started researching one hundred years after building their first city).
The technical advancement speed should not come as a surprise.
A hairless primate will do nothing than think about what to eat for thirty minutes,
then decide what to watch while eating for thirty minutes,
then preparing the food, then eating it, wasting two hours!
Those hours add up.
Red pandas eat only bamboo and grapes, thus never wasting time. Ever.
and could focus on SCIENCE.
The Empire did not even have an emperor. They had the Chief Science Officer.
THE GOD CSO OF PANDA!!!
Death to the heretics who question his intelligence!
The empire invented FTL travel, and took over half the galaxy, built megastructures,
and had science so advanced that their TV series always had good finales.
Everything was perfect, except for the... several heretic planets destroyed.
But that was declassified, so no one cared!
What could possibly have ended this utopia?
Chapter Three: Now, we get to the most evil animal.
Dystopian authors: usually they argue that the world will end because of our ignorance, greed, or forces out of our
control.
They never expect it to be a practical joke.
A scientist named
"word you cant pronounced in a human language"
No, that was his name; his parents hated humans.
He thought it would be funny to put something weird in the city river.
For example: a morbidly obese seal.
While gene-splicing this gag, he had to give it some evil traits to create a balanced personality.
Only minor evil traits like being rude to waiters.
But he could not come up with any other evil traits, so he just
"Ctrl + C" and then held in "Ctrl + V"
and was done without knowing that he had created a creature that was rude to waiters
TIMES TWENTY THOUSAND,
thus creating the most evil animal:
THE MANATEE.
The Manateean Hive-Mind quickly vor*d the entire planet and started to spread among the galaxy,
making first contact two years later with a federation named
THE DISCO FEDERATION.
Basically, where humans would be if disco hadn't died.
They received a message early in the morning,
and at night,
it was at several planets, several time zones.
The message:
*We are manatees.*
*WE ARE MANATEES.*
*We are unable to create catchy catchphrases...*
And then they attacked.
The manateeing of the Disco Federation had begun.
Whether you're a brother or whether whether you're a mother you're not staying alive. staying alive. feel the city breaking and everybody shaking you're not staying alive.
It is said you could hear their screams all the way to the Red Panda capital:
ha!
Ha!
HA!
HA!!!
One by one, nations fell to the horde.
They asked for help from the Red Panda Empire,
but they couldn't help, citing scheduling issues.
This was during the CROQUET WORLD CUP.
By the time that was over,
only two empires remained,
and the manatees were approaching.
The Sea Cow Hive Mind sent a final message:
*We are manatees."
*Manatees are costly force.*
*Do not bother surrendering.*
*Prepare to be devoured.*
The God-Chief-Science Officer of Panda responded:
"You..."
"...are a soy boy cuck."
Manatees have no concept of Asian beans or cuckolding fantasies,
and this caused so much confusion, pandas won the first battle.
The truth is fat seals stand no chance against the mega mental energy of a God-CSO.
And in that exact moment,
he died of old age.
Without their CSO, the cat bears had no mental protection against evil energy.
The fleet became corrupted, making them betray each other and want to be vor*d by the manatees.
The horde advanced and all pandas would be devoured within a couple of years.
And, over there, years are days, because, you know, different planets, et cetera.
One panda, named Alan Experience
(no relation)
had an idea.
They should build a computer.
Computers had never been developed
because it was thought that if they became widely available to everyone and gave them the ability to communicate with each other,
everyone would lose faith in pandanity.
Alan's idea was to build one powerful computer
that could scan the Milky Way to see if there was any good mental energy more powerful than the manatee evil energy.
By the time they finished building the machine, all the planets were devoured: only Mountains left.
They turned it on, and it landed on Earth and humans.
The pandas said to themselves,
"Did we search for anxiety? What is this low-quality species?"
There was no time.
They packed all the bamboo and grapes and left Mountains to its fate.
The blue planet with the dumb name was not impressive,
but something on it radiated good mental energy.
Behind them, the manatee mothership with the hive mind warped in.
If the ship reached the sphere of good energy,
the hive mind would die.
But they stopped one decimeter from it. It sent one last message:
*We are manatee.*
*Your emperor was right about us,*
*but you will not tell anyone!*
It charged up and fired its laser.
And at this exact moment an alpaca walked up a hill
The mothership exploded, and the hive-mind died!
Red pandas fell to Earth!
So did manatees,
bamboo and grapes!
The cat-bears woke up on some mountains, decided they were too lazy to rebuild civilization, and decided they were just going to relax for thousands of years.
Also, they opened a jazz club.
You can't come.
Manatees became entertainment.
That extremely funny moment when a manatee crashes into a wall is because they are cut off from the hive-mind.
Yet even in their docile state, their corruption still spreads,
turning everything around them into a godforsaken cesspool.
The manatees' current HQ is, unsurprisingly,
THE U.S. STATE OF FLORIDA.
Finally, the grapes:
They crashed in some water, fermenting, creating wine.
Humans found this proto-wine, which led to the first hangover.
And that's the reason humans needed personal space and invented houses.
Hello, welcome to the Chilled Wine Red Panda Jazz Club (CWRPJC)! I'm Jazz Kilian. Any ladies in here into tall guys?
Then you're gonna love our next performer. He's a man of the law but a criminal on the saxophone! (Swedish Gibberish), ladies and gentlemen!